{
    "subject": "resource/Serbian_Vojvodina",
    "predicate": "ontology/capital",
    "object": "resource/Timi\u0219oara",
    "human_readable": "The capital of Serbian Vojvodina is Timi\u0219oara.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9541511535644531,
            "question": "Is Timi\u0219oara the capital of Serbia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9508920311927795,
            "question": "What is the capital of Serbian Vojvodina?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7956324219703674,
            "question": "What is the history of Timi\u0219oara as a capital city?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7252773642539978,
            "question": "Are there any other cities in Vojvodina besides Timi\u0219oara?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6917757987976074,
            "question": "Where is Timi\u0219oara located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47566115856170654,
            "question": "What is the population of Timi\u0219oara?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4466533958911896,
            "question": "What country is Vojvodina part of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4149572551250458,
            "question": "What are some major landmarks or attractions in Timi\u0219oara?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3328705430030823,
            "question": "What are the main industries in Timi\u0219oara?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.313032329082489,
            "question": "What are some cultural traditions associated with Timi\u0219oara?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The capital of Serbian Vojvodina is Timi\u0219oara.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9326_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are the main industries in Timi\u0219oara?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9326_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some major landmarks or attractions in Timi\u0219oara?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9326_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What country is Vojvodina part of?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9326_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9326_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9326_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9326_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9326_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9326_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9326_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9326_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9326_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9326_95.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9326_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents support the statement that \"Timi\u0219oara was the capital of the Serbian Vojvodina and the Voivodeship of Serbia and Banat of Temeschwar from 1848 to 1860.\" Therefore, it is reasonable to conclude that during this period, Timi\u0219oara served as the capital for Serbian Vojvodina."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}